Dateline Tarantulon 6.
The brave warriors of Earth,
under the command of General
Major Webelo Zapp Brannigan,
have achieved victory
over the Spider homeworld.
And to the victor belong the spoils.
One trillion dollars in silken treasure.
Mm.
My fellow Earthicans,
after meeting with top voodoo economists,
I have decided to refund
our silk surplus to you, the taxpayers.
That's right.
I've sent you each 300 buckaroos
in the form of a Tricky Dick fun bill.
Knock yourselves out.
I'm slightly richer.
What to do? What to do?
One $300 hookerbot or 300 $1 hookerbots?
I'm going to swim with a whale.
They're the gentle giants of the deep.
I'm well aware of that.
Scruffy's going to get himself
one of them $300 haircuts.
This one's lost its pizzazz.
A fortune, it is.
At last, Zoidberg
will live like a rich man.
Go away. Get away from me.
Shmeesh. It's just 300 bucks.
What is that, like,
a hundred cups of coffee?
That's it!
I'm getting a hundred cups of coffee,
starting now.
Coffee machine, one cup of coffee, please.
Smells good.
Leela, are you there?
- No.
- Oh, yes, you are.
I'm hereby inviting you
and your oddball coworkers
to a special reception
to display the national silk surplus.
I believe you know the heroic
space stallion who captured it.
Show them my medal, Kif.
He rented it with his tax refund.
So, Leela, will you have the pleasure?
What little there is to be had.
Tomorrow night at 8:00, then.
Smooches. Mwah.
No cheap crack houses for me no more.
Very good, sir.
Shall I pre-warm sir's crack pipe?
Oh, Kif, it was so romantic of you
to rent this paddle plane
with your tax rebate.
We're like two dandelion seeds
wafting on the breeze.
Yes. Seeds. Wafting.
I almost feel kind of shallow
for blowing my rebate
on this cool talking tattoo.
Hey, Gordon Gecko.
I cost as much as this whole crummy date.
Shut up!
Ow!
Ma'am, it has become too much of a chore
for me to clean out my wrinkles each day.
Is it true that stem cells
may fight the aging process?
Well, yes, in the same way
an infant may fight Muhammad Ali, but...
One pound of stem cells, please.
Of course, any age-reversing effects
will be purely temporary...
Oh.
Ooh.
Ooh-hoo-hoo.
Oh! Oh-ho-ho-ho-ho.
Say, buddy, why is
this Grand Cigar so pricey?
Well, as you can see,
its wrapper is a piece
of the original U.S. Constitution.
It was hand-rolled by Queen Elizabeth
during her wild years
and was buried with George Burns
until grave-robbing space mushrooms...
Well, you know the rest.
Give you 300 bucks for it.
- No can do.
- Oh, all right.
I'll just take these
$300 burglar's tools, then.
Very good, sir.
So, uh, what time you close tonight?
Hey, Pops. Did that tax rebate come?
Came and went.
You're now the proud owner
of Bamboo Boogie Boots.
With a warning label this big,
you know they got to be fun.
But, Pops, I don't want to have fun.
I want to be like you...
Boring, but prudently invested.
Babylon's bells!
I tallied almost 300 bananas
on this entertainment product.
Now you put them on and have fun.
I don't wanna!
Well, then I'm gonna put them on
and make you watch me have fun.
See? Fun, fun...
Dwight! Help me!
I'll save you, Pops.
Hey!
Turn that damn music...
Up.
Isn't this fun?
No! I wish I had two mommies.
Try these, uh, sir.
I ask for rich guy stuff,
and you give me shiny pebbles?
Bah!
I bid you adieu.
Ah!
I'd like a pass
to swim with Mushu, please.
Well, you asked the right guy.
I'm the whale biologist.
Though, personally, I hate whales.
Especially Mushu.
Then why'd you become a whale biologist?
I don't know you well enough
to get into that.
$300 please.
Noon tomorrow.
If you're late, you only get to tread
water in the scallop tank.
Yeah, I'll have a coffee.
Guppy, trout, mermaid or...
Whale, please.
Amy, I... I also spent
some of my tax rebate
on a gift for you.
Oh, Kiffy.
It shows the time
wherever we both are.
And it's powered by love.
Also, you have to wind it.
Ooh! Somebody won big at skeeball.
You shut up.
I love it, Kif.
I'll use it whenever I want
to know what time it is.
Ooh, it's Fry and Leela.
Hi, Fry and Leela!
Ah!
Ooh! Oh, my... Keep pedaling.
Oh, for the love of God, keep pedaling.
Phew.
Bye, Fry and Leela!
Oh.
Oh!
I can't wait till the tattoos
on Amy's butt hear about this.
- Hear about what?
- Tell us!
Don't feel sad, my little tadpole.
I'm trying not to.
But my gift to you
is in the belly of a whale.
Say, this reminds me of that time
I ate that other watch Kif gave you.
Hey, it is kind of like that.
To induce vomiting, that was the solution.
Everywhere, it went.
What a Valentine's Day that was.
Hmm.
This may seem like a huge coincidence,
but I happen to have
an "in" with that whale.
Scruffy's formulated a plan.
But you'll need a ready source
of nauseating rotten fish.
Freshen your coffee, sir?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Keep it coming.
Put the pot down. Get away!
You're so young in spirit.
It's hard to believe you're as old as 25.
The key is to grab life by the ho-jos.
Live every day like it might be your last.
What'll it be, kids?
One bowl of mild farina.
Pay dirt.
Hi-ya!
Here you go, big spender.
Foie gras and caviar.
Goose liver?
Fish eggs? Feh!
Where's the goose? Where's the fish?
Hey, that's what rich people eat,
the garbage parts of the food.
I ate garbage yesterday
and it didn't cost me $300!
I'm not paying!
Farewell, good sir.
The Grand Cigar, she is mine.
And with absolutely no consequences.
You see that?
Grand theft tobacco.
Time to get off
our fat cop asses and ride.
Pee-ew!
This fish is slightly too rotten
to even make jambalaya.
So far, so good.
Where's Kif?
This isn't Yemeni, it's Sulawesi.
And the cup's shaking.
I don't want my coffee shaking.
You seem a tad wound up, buddy.
And your face is greasy.
Real greasy. You been up all night?
Of course I've been up all night!
Not because of caffeine. It was insomnia.
I couldn't stop thinking about coffee.
I need a nap.
Coffee time!
Ah. Mighty fine smokable.
Fancy cigar?
Why don't you smoke it already?
Puff, puff. Go, go, go!
Nah, you can't blow a smoke
from such a majestic stogie
in just anyone's face.
I'm saving it for the fancy pantses
at Zapp Brannigan's black-tie reception.
You coming?
And the fifth reason whales kill
is for the sheer fun of it.
Anything else?
Yeah, you're lumpy and you smell awful.
Hey. I calls them like I sees them.
I'm a whale biologist.
Okay, Mushu, it's feeding time.
Oh, crud, he ate my suit.
The suit was ugly.
Whale biologist.
Perhaps if you tighten your grip, sir.
Ah, thank you, golf slave.
Bah! Rich people wouldn't waste
their time on this nonsense.
Plus, these eggs are gritty and tasteless.
Ow! Not so rough!
Ladies and gentlemen, presenting Mushu,
the educated whale
who thinks he's better than you.
Come on, Mushu, barf!
Barf like a freshman!
And now, ignorant whale lovers,
we'll see who's boss
as I make Mushu jump through this hoop.
Jump, Mushu.
Who wants a fish?
Mushu is sad.
It just keeps coming and coming.
Wait, that chunk!
It's the watch.
I got it, Amy, I got it.
The plan went off without a...
He's got aquarium property! Stop him!
Better do what he says.
He's a whale biologist.
You're under arrest, you squishy punk!
Oh...
Oh.
The Spiderians, though weak
and womanlike on the battlefield,
are masters of the textile arts.
Taste like King Crab, by the way.
Crazy bugs actually wove this tapestry
of my heroic conquest
while I was still killing them.
What? It's not even scratch-and-sniff?
But if rich people think it's good,
I'll buy it.
One art, please.
What a clever impersonation
of a stupid poor person!
How much is that place mat
actually worth, Brannigan?
Exactly $1 billion.
Now that's walkin' around money.
What? Hey?
So I said to Kitty,
"The only way to keep the butler from
running away is to cut off his foot."
Ah-ha-ha.
Uh-huh.
Yes, it reminds me of a joke I heard
about upper middle-class people.
I've never been sad
at a party before.
I wonder if my mind is thinking
about Kif being in jail.
Jail's not so bad.
You can make sangria in the toilet.
Course, it's shank or be shanked.
Of course.
Look, just give back our property
and we'll drop the charges.
Fine! Have the watch!
It's broken anyway.
I don't want your watch!
You're covered in precious ambergris.
Precious hamburgers?
"Ambergris." Noun.
A grease-like product
of the sperm whale's digestive tract
that is used as a base
in the finest perfumes.
This has been Roseanne,
your guide to the world of facts.
You heard Roseanne.
Scrape off the priceless ambergris
and I'll let you go.
Or better yet, I'll simply shed my skin.
Stop it. Stop it. It's fine!
I will destroy you!
Wha...
Uh, got to go.
Uh, fight club.
What's happening, Hubie?
Ah, I'm afraid the face
you fell in love with
was actually just a blob of living gunk
I bought with my tax refund.
Well, as long as we're being honest,
I also spent my tax refund
on a crazy treatment.
That certainly is honest.
It's better for us to both
just be ourselves.
You, wrinkled as a prune.
You, fat as the queen of sea cows.
I love you!
So, you see, the putrid, waxy substance
I was coated with was...
Not precious ambergris?
Yes. And I managed to sneak some out
in the usual place.
Ta-da!
Using that, I'll make you a perfume
of lilac and jasmine and Franken Berry.
Oh, Kif, it's so romantic.
I can't even wait!
I'm going to wear it right now.
Bah!
Who smells like freaking porpoise hork?
I do. Kiss me, Kif.
Oh, what a foolish squid I've been.
I'm not rich.
I can't even buy one measly masterpiece.
Pardon us, gent.
Might a couple of hungry, hungry hoboes
take a feed from that aluminum snack box?
So now I'm in the gutter
surrounded by bums who eat garbage?
Money brought me no happiness.
Bubkes.
Ooh, this boot's got
a little pudding at the bottom.
Interestingly, the Spiderians
are more closely related
to our elephants than our spiders.
Don't mind us. Whoa, whoa!
The loot! The loot!
The loot is on fire!
Leela, my precious rock dove,
I'll save you.
Everyone, to the fire door!
It's on fire!
We're trapped, my sweet hippopotamus.
Coffee, coffee, coffee!
- Where are we, Pops?
- Wha...
What happened to the food?
I think we were saved
by a mysterious orange blur.
Welcome, one and all.
I finally figured out
how money could make me happy,
by using it to buy
my hungry friends a feast!
Everyone join us.
Oysters Rockefeller here
has provided genuine turkey dogs!
Heck, you're never too rich
to enjoy a free turkey dog.
- Yeah, I'm starved!
- All right!
- I'll take four.
- Me, too.
Oh, what the hell.
Here, Dwight.
The boots only cost $299.99.
You invest this penny like you wanted.
Thanks, Dad.
I'm going to take this and buy
five shares of Amazon.com.
A risk-taker!
That's my boy.
The entire surplus is gone!
Oh, what a McGovern I've been.
Why did I have to issue
that crooked tax rebate?
Uh, at least we got a few mildly
interesting stories out of it.
Oh, my, yes.
Speaking of which,
my story kind of petered out
without me learning a lesson.
There he is!
All right! Closure!
"Futurama." Noun.
Um, I don't know,
you just watched it, dummy.
What are you asking me for?
Hey, here's a fun definition, "Idiot."
Noun.
You!
This has been Roseanne,
your guide to the world of facts.